Finding Aid for the Joe Menosky papers, 1983-2005, (bulk 1995-2001) LSC.2250
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1970s, 1990s-2004
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - revision, (1999 June 8) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctory Spy - production reports, (1999 June-Sep) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: TV research (related to ratings), (2000 May 17) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: two hour story and bible, (1994 Feb 16) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Unimatrix 0 - Handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Unimatrix Zero - final draft script, (2000 March 16) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Unimatrix Zero, Part Two - beat sheet and handwritten notes, (2000 May 5) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Unimatrix Zero, Part Two - script, (2000 June 5) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: visual effects budget summary, (1998 May 29) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager '96, Episode 1 - The Summer of '67 story outline, (1996 June 24) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager '96, Episode 2 - Who is Martin Barrows?, (undated) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager '96, Parts I & II - preliminary story outline, (1996 June 25) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - Act Two script material, (1999 Aug 24) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - beat sheet and handwritten notes, (1999 Aug 19-20) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - final draft script, (1999 Aug 31) (Box 8)
    WATER DAMAGED--NEED TO PHOTOCOPY
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - first draft script, (1999 Aug 23) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - first draft script, (1999 Aug 23) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - first draft script, (1999 Aug 23) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - first draft script, (1999 Aug 24) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - first draft script, (1999 Aug 24) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Voyager Conspiracy (The) - preliminary draft story proposal, (1999 Aug 11) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: War Game - story outline, (1997 Oct 20) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Writers'/Directors Guide, First Season Version, (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Writers-Directors Guide, (1996-1997) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Xindi (The) - final draft script, (2003 June 17) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Year of Hell - first draft script, (1997 July 28) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Year of Hell, Part 2 - script material, (1999) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Year of Hell, Part II - first draft script, (1997 Aug 7) (Box 11)
  - Taken draft script (spec script), (mid-1980s) (Box 31)
  - Trek Nation documentary production packet and press kit, (2005 Jan 31) (Box 15)
    Sent to Trek writers at Paramount.
  - Witch Hunter Robin: DVD set, (undated) (Box 27)
    3 DVDs.
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: Hostage - draft script, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: notes and research, (2003) (Box 26)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: Pilot episode - draft script, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: Series Bible, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: Water Witch - draft script, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Witch Hunter Robin: Witch Doctor - draft script, (undated) (Box 26)
- Motion Picture Projects, mostly undated
  The motion picture series includes materials representing Adult Ed, The Bullwinkle Syndrome, and Companions, among others. The series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  - Adult Ed: draft script, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: Fundamental Trouble - draft script, (undated) (Box 34)
    May have been produced as Hiding Out
  - Adult Ed: Fundamental Trouble - draft script, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: Fundamental Trouble - draft script, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Fundamental Trouble - draft script, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Fundamental Trouble - script material, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: Last Two Thirds - synopsis, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: scene outlines with annotations, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: script material, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: script material, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: script material, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (1986 April 23) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script and handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: Welcome to the Real World - draft script and handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: draft script, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Adult Ed: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 33)
  - Adult Ed: script, (undated) (Box 34)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) draft screenlay, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) draft screenlay, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) draft script re-write, (1986) (Box 36)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) first draft script, (1984) (Box 36)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 35)
  - Bullwinkle Syndrome (The) handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 2)
    Appears to be unproduced.
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino publicity book, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino research, (1990 June) (Box 28)
  - Carlo Mollino research, (undated) (Box 28)
  - Companions draft script, (1984 March 13) (Box 37)
  - Companions draft script, (1984 March 3) (Box 37)
  - Companions draft script, (undated) (Box 37)
  - Companions draft script and sales receipts, (1984 April) (Box 37)
  - Companions draft script and script material, (undated) (Box 37)
  - Companions first draft script, (1984 March 5) (Box 37)
  - Companions first re-write screenplay, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 37)
  - Companions handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions handwritten notes and story outline, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions screenplay, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions screenplay, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions screenplay, (undated) (Box 36)
  - Companions script material, (1983) (Box 36)
  - Companions script material and handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 37)
  - Companions second re-write script, (1984 March 1) (Box 37)
  - Companions second re-write script, (undated) (Box 37)
  - Freddy vs Jason beat outline and story outlines, (1995) (Box 7)
  - Memo from Menosky to Braga regarding La Scorta, (1994 July 25) (Box 31)
  - Million Pound Note (The) draft script, (2001 Dec 1) (Box 16)
    Appears to be unproduced
  - Mission Impossible 2 plot commentary, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Omen (The) remake proposal, (2005 March 21) (Box 26)
  - Oracle For Those Who Can't draft script, (1995 Nov) (Box 31)
    Short film script submitted to a British short film contest.
- Submissions to Menosky/Informal Consulting, 1990s-2002
  The bulk of the series includes story outlines, notes, and script material for a variety of projects submitted to Menosky for consulation. Includes Star Trek IX, Star Trek Enterprise, Star Trek Nemesis, and Star Trek Resurrection, among others. The series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  - Lightspeed story outline, (undated) (Box 7)
  - Speed Racer story treatment, (2000 Nov 28) (Box 22)
  - Star Trec Resurrection second draft script, (1996 Jan 8) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Battle Cry draft script, (2000 Nov 9) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Andorian Incident (The) - first draft script, (2001 Aug 9) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Andorian Incident (The) - first draft script, (2001 Aug 9) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Assault on Memory Alpha - story outline, (undated) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Assault on Memory Alpha - story outline, (undated) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Beat sheets, handwritten notes, and series bible, (undated) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Bible, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Brannon Braga notes, (2000 Aug 10) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - dailies log, (2001 May 24) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - draft script, (2001 Feb 22) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - final draft script, (2001 May 1) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - final draft script, (2001 May 1) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - final draft script, (2001 May 4) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - first draft script, (2000 Oct 9) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - first draft script, (2000 Oct 9) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - notes and story outline, (2000 Aug) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - photocopied storyboards and shooting notes, (2001) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Aug 25) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Aug 25) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Oct 27) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Oct 27) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Sep 18) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2000 Sep 22) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, (2001 Feb 22) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 16) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 17) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 18) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 21) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 22) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 23) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 24) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Aug 24) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Nov 1) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Nov 1) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Oct) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Oct 27) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Sep 1) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Sep 11) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Sep 22) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2000 Sep 8) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2001 Feb 14) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2001 Feb 21) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2001 May 11) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material, (2001 May 22) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material (Folder 1 of 2), (2001 May 25) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material (Folder 2 of 2), (2001 May 25) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script material and memo with notes, (2001 Feb 14) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - script, production information, and memos, (2001) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - shooting schedule, (2001 May-June) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - shooting schedule and notes, (2001 July) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - shot lists and handwritten notes, (2001 April-May) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Broken Bow - third draft script, (2001 Feb 22) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Call sheets, (2001 May) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Character profiles and series Bible, (undated) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Character renderings (photocopies), (2001 April 4) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Concept presentation, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Die You Naughty Bastard - script material, (2000 July 10) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Episode 3 beat sheet, (2001 March 16) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Episode 3 beat sheet, (2001 March 16) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Episode Two - script material, (undated) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Episode Two - script material, (undated) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Episode Two - script material, (undated) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Fight or Flight - final draft script, (2001 May 1) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Fight or Flight - revised final draft script, (2001 June 27) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Fight or Flight - script pages, (2001 May 1) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Fight or Flight - second draft script, (2001 April 27) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: first season thoughts, (2001 April 24) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: handwritten notes, (2000 April 28) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Kerry McCluggates notes, (2000 Oct 23) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Last of the Runakhans (The) - story outline, (undated) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: list of potential writers, (2001 May 15) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: memo from Braga re. Studio notes and more, (2001 Jan 31) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: memo re. Timing Sheet, (2001 June 7) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: memos from Brannon Braga to Rick Berman, (2000 June-July) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: memos from Brannon Braga to Rick Berman, (2000 May-July) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: memos from Brannon Braga to Rick Berman, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Night in Sickbay (A) - final draft script, (2002 July 18) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Other People's Wars - story outline, (2001 April 25) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Other People's Wars - story outline, (2001 April 25) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot Episode - handwritten notes, (2000 May 24) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot episode - handwritten notes, character sketches, and memos, (2001) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot Episode - story outlines, (2000 June) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot Episode - story outlines, (2000 May) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot Episode - story treatments, (2000 Aug) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot episode notes (holograph), (2001 July-Aug) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot episode notes and story outline, (2000 Aug) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot episode staff contact list, (2001 May 14) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: pilot script review, (2001 April 21) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: post production procedures and contact list, (2001 July) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: script material for unknown episode, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: script pages, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: season one post production schedule, (2001 May 25) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: series pitch, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: series pitch memo, (undated) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: series proposal, (1999 July) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: series proposal, (1999 July 14) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: series synopsis, (undated) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: shooting schedule (no episode title), (2001 June) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (2000 Oct) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (2000 Oct 9) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (2001 April 16) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (2001 May 4) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (2001 May 4) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: story idea, (undated) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Strange New World - final draft script, (2001 July 6) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Strange New World - script material, (2001 May 15) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - beat sheet, (2001 May 14) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - first draft script, (2001 July 30) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - first draft script, (2001 June 6) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - first draft story outline, (2001 May 8) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - story outline, (undated) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Terra Nova - story outline, (undated) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Tulsa - story outline, (2001 March 19) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Twilight on Nova Runner - story outline, (undated) (Box 23)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Unexpected - final draft script, (2001 July 26) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Untitled Vulcan Station - beat sheet, (2001 May 23) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: Untitled Vulcan/Human Cultural Perspective Story - story outline, (2001 April 25) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Enterprise: video processing log, (2001 June 22) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek First Contact - press kit, (undated) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek First Contact: call sheets, (1996 April-July) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek First Contact: Memos, notes and research, (1995 March-Nov) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek First Contact: movie reviews (photocopied clippings), (1996 Nov) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek First Contact: press kit, (undated) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek First Contact: publicity stills, (undated) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Generations II: shooting schedule and notes, (1996) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Generations II: shooting schedules, (1996 June) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Generations II: shooting schedules, (1996 March) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Generations II: staff and crew list, (1996 May 27) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Generations: publicity postcards, (c. 1994) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek IX: script, (1997 Nov 14) (Box 5)
    May have been produced as Star Trek Insurrection
  - Star Trek IX: story outline, (1997 June 23) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek IX: story synopsis, (1997 June 3) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Nemesis: draft script, (2001 Feb 12) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Nemesis: first draft script, (2001 Feb 12) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: draft script, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: notes and summaries, (1995-1996) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: script, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: script, (undated) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: script material, (1996 April 1) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: script material, (1996 April 24) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: script material, (1996 April 25) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Resurrection: story outline, (1995 June 2) (Box 24)
  - Star Trek Stardust draft script, (1997 Sep 11) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: notes and script material, (1996) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: The Movie - first draft script, (1993 July 2) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: The Movie - Second draft script, (1993 Sep 1) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek VIII: memo re: budget, (1996 Feb 21) (Box 1)
  - Tomb Raider script, (2000 May 19) (Box 11)
  - Tomb Raider script material, (undated) (Box 22)
- Articles by Menosky, early-1980s
  Series contains a small number of publications with pieces written by Menosky. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - 47 - article, galley proof, handwritten notes, and memos, (1983) (Box 38)
  - Science 80, (1980 July-Aug) (Box 38)
    Contains article by Menosky
  - Science 80, (1980 Sep-Oct) (Box 38)
  - Science 81, (1981 April) (Box 38)
  - Science 81, (1981 July-Aug) (Box 38)
  - Science 81, (1981 Sep) (Box 38)
  - Science 82, (1982 Jan-Feb) (Box 38)
  - Science 83, (1983 Sep) (Box 38)
  - Science Books & Films, (1981 May-June) (Box 38)
  - Technology Review, (1983 May-June) (Box 38)
  - Transcript of interview with Charles T. Tart, (1980) (Box 38)
- Publications and Memorabilia, 1964, 1968, 1979, 1994-2002
  The series is primarily published books and memorabilia related to the Star Trek franchise. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - Arrow of Time: A Voyage Through Science to Solve Time's Greatest Mystery (The) -book, (c. 1990) (Box 6)
  - Cinefantastique magazine, (1997 Nov) (Box 18)
    Star Trek Deep Space Nine featured on the cover
  - Daily Variety, (2000 July 13) (Box 14)
    Includes story on Brannon Braga
  - Dead Zone (The) - book, (c. 1979) (Box 6)
  - Deep Space and Sacred Time: Star Trek in the American Mythos - book, (c. 1998) (Box 6)
  - Details Magazine, (1997 Oct) (Box 18)
    Jeri Ryan featured on the cover.
  - Enterprise Zones: Critical Positions on Star Trek - book, (c. 1996) (Box 6)
  - Entertainment Weekly, (1995 Oct 27) (Box 10)
  - Federation News, Year 2, Issue 4 - Voyager Edition, (undated) (Box 15)
  - Future Perfect: How Star Trek Conquered Planet Earth - book, (c. 1998) (Box 6)
  - Inside Star Trek, (2000-2001) (Box 15)
    4 issues.
  - Inside Star Trek magazine, (2000 Sep) (Box 19)
  - Making of Star Trek (The) - book, (c. 1968) (Box 6)
  - Meaning of Star Trek (The) - book, (c. 1997) (Box 6)
  - Mythomania: Fantasies, Fables, and Sheer Lies in Contemporary American Popular Art - book, (c. 1996) (Box 41)
  - NASA/Trek: Popular Science and Sex in America - book, (c. 1997) (Box 6)
  - Quotable Star Trek - book, (c. 1999) (Box 6)
  - Sci Fi Entertainment Magazine, (1996 Dec) (Box 14)
    Star Trek Issue.
  - Star Trek and Sacred Ground: Explorations of Star Trek, Religion, and American Culture - book, (c. 1999) (Box 6)
  - Star Trek Chronology: The History of the Future - book, (c. 1996) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Communicator, (1998) (Box 10)
  - Star Trek Encyclopedia: A Reference Guide to the Future (The) - hard cover book, (c. 1994) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Encyclopedia: A Reference Guide to the Future (The) - soft bound book, (c. 1994) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Format, (1964 March 11) (Box 15)
    Appears to be a pitch or propal for the original Star Trek television series. (Collected by Menosky)
  - Star Trek Italian Fan Club magazines, photos, and stickers, (1994) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek Magazine, (1998-1999) (Box 10)
    5 issues.
  - Star Trek Magazine, (2000 Nov) (Box 29)
    Number 72.
  - Star Trek Starfleet Command pouch with dog tags, (undated) (Box 40)
    Gift given to the writing staff for one of the Christmas seasons.
  - Star Trek The Magazine, (2002 Dec) (Box 6)